# MANUELE FRAU

UI/UX DESIGNER

CASE STUDIES AVAILABLE ON behance.net/manuelefrau

ITALIA +39 333 3878202 SUOMI +358 417248370

July 2019 - December 2021

manuelefraucontact@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/manuele-frau

# **PROFILE**

I am a career changer with strong customer service experience gained in the hospitality and food industries, I like to help others. I am also a musician, sound artist and audio engineer. I have a deep artistic mindset and I like to solve problems, I feel satisfied when I achieve goals.

I recently become a UI/UX designer and I have basic coding skills. I would love to work for a company or agency where I can grow while expressing my creativity.

### SKILLS

My key skills are:

- Visual design
- Interaction design
- Branding
- Typography & Iconography
- Style guides
- Mobile app design
- User research and testing
- User personas
- User flows
- · Wireframing & prototyping

Proficient with design tools such as:

- Sketch
- Adobe XD
- InVision
- Affinity Photo
- Photoshop
- Flinto
- Blender
- Atom/Visual Studio Code
- \* If you use different tools that works well in your workflow, I would be happy to learn it.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

Resturant Shift Supervisor
Fafa's Plats Oy • Helsinki, Finland

Front Desk Agent April 2015 - March 2019

Dharma Hotel & Luxury Suites • Rome, Italy

Freelance Audio Technician 2013 - 2015

Radiospeaker • Rome, Italy

Freelance Production Assistant 2011 - 2013

Kick Agency • Rome, Italy

### EDUCATION

UI Design Bootcamp 2021 - 2022

Career Foundry • Online Course

Frontend Development for Designers 2021 - 2022

Career Foundry • Online Course

Front Desk Agent Course 2015

CTS Tourism School • Rome, Italy

Sound Engineering Course 2013

Adriatico Institute • Rome, Italy

Fine Art Diploma 2000 - 2005

ISA RM2 Art Institute • Rome, Italy

#### LANGUAGES

EnglishItalianSpanishFinnishFluentNativeBasicVery Low